http://www.paldat.org/privacy;jsessionid=5FD34E0F354A9BD1CA5D7433D7DAFBFA

Forgot your password?New to PalDat?Username
Password
Remember MeHomeSearch DataSubmit DataTerminologyInformationHow to use PalDatGet PicturesRegisterGeneral Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
Information
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) improves transparency and data privacy rights of individuals and is taking effect in Europe in May 25, 2018. (DSGVO, TKG 2003). We want to inform you about the most important aspects of data processing within our website.
You have the right to get information, correction, deletion, limitation, data portability, and objection. If you believe that the processing of your data violates data protection law, you can complain to the supervisory authority. In Austria, this is the data protection authority.
Your personal data in PalDat
This privacy statement describes how PalDat collects and uses the personal information you provide on our websites.
The personal information that we collect will depend on how you are using the PalDat Websites:
If you are registered in PalDat, the palynological database of the University of Vienna, we store the following personal data from you: title, first name, last name, e-mail address, address or company address. These data (title, first name, last name, e-mail address, address or company address) are stored on a server at the University of Vienna, and exclusively used for e-mail contacts.
In connection with your creation of a PalDat account (registeration), we collect your name, email address, username, and password, as well as other information you may provide.
To enable your access to the PalDat website and databases through your library or institution, we may collect information concerning the institution’s internet protocol address, your username and password, or other authentication methods.
We may collect personally identifiable information in connection with statements you may post on the comments page.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer) or the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac).
This website is an official publication organ of the “Society for the Promotion of Palynological Research in Austria”. Your Name (first name and last name) is listed with your publication(s) (author, picture credits, picture legend, author of diagnosis, literature references, list of “Contributors”). See also our “Terms of Conditions”.
If you do not agree, please let us know per mail (autpal@univie.ac.at) or by post at any time. We will then immediately delete your personal data from the server.
If you contact us by e-mail, your data will be stored on a local computer at the department for the purpose of processing the request and in case of follow-up questions. This data will not be disclosed to third parties.
Newsletter
If you are registered for the PalDat newsletter, you indicated that you would like to receive news about current publications. If you no longer want to receive information from us, you can log in at the PalDat website any time with your access data and unsubscribe from the newsletter. To sign-off the PalDat newsletter go to “My profile”. By the same way you can subscribe again for the newsletter with your access data at any time.
Contact
PalDat
Department of Botany and Biodiversity Research
University of Vienna
Rennweg 14
A-1030 Vienna, Austria
Telefon: +43 1 4277 54100
Email: info@paldat.org
